You won't believe it,
you sell it at the Cocoa Show,
man AI won't believe it.
Today I will appeal.
Wow, how nice.
Good morning all good.
It was half past nine and where is it?
Hi it was half past nine.
Hmm.
I fix who is responsible I fix who is the manager?
Sorry you're in charge of the store.
What is your name Larissa?
I fall and fix that I came here to fix your day let me
explain I'm Caio from the Passenger's workshop.
And this little ball here of Larissa chocolate,
it contains 20g of happiness and how much happiness you need on your day today.
Very,
very much ours.
I'll buy 1 just for you.
Nice guy sold one on the Cocoa Show.
Hope you like it from the heart closed.
I'm Caio from the Brigadier's workshop.
he's great
ー.
I'm going to give away a hundred reais because
this guy was a lot of good people.
Wow,
he takes good care of me,
I'll send him a hundred.
He deserves.
He's a wonderful Passenger.
His marketing was perfect.
Haha
I am not eating chocolate but I will buy it from you for your marketing.
I'm going to take it so to my mother I'm going to want 1 box so
I'm going to take 2 I'm going to take my 1st our beat here to
buy for advertising because I'm clogged with doubt ok?
The advertisement was top notch.
Fix your Gustavo day.
I wanted to know how much happiness you need.
Haha.